00B2DB<h3>My Story</h3>
                                  <p>I began my creative career in the First Grade, when I won a local coloring contest. Ever since, I've been creating illustrations and designs using everything from watercolors and colored pencils to Adobe Creative Suite and Sketch.</p>
                                    <p>After graduating from Southwestern University in Communications, I worked in Creative Staffing where I helped Lead Designers, Art Directors and Creative Teams find Digital Creative talent. I learned all about the field of UI/UX and took classes at the Art Institute of Austin and General Assembly and in 2017, I completed an immersive UI Design program.</p>
                                    <p>Now my passion for art and drawing, combined with my experience in the digital creative industry, give me the unique ability to create informed and functional designs.</p>
                                       <p>When I'm not sketching on my ipad or watching Bob's Burgers, you'll find me running at LadyBird lake, swimming laps at Deep Eddy, or sipping on a fromar (frozen margarita) at Matt's El Rancho.</p>